{
    "subject": "resource/K._J._Stevens",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Minimalism",
    "human_readable": "K. J. Stevens was associated with Minimalism.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8872984051704407,
            "question": "Who was K. J. Stevens associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7525672912597656,
            "question": "Name another artist associated with Minimalism."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5198736786842346,
            "question": "What were some of the influences on Minimalism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4704101085662842,
            "question": "What artistic movement is K. J. Stevens linked to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4664013683795929,
            "question": "Give an example of a work associated with the Minimalist movement."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4503500461578369,
            "question": "Can you name an artist known for Minimalism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2879987061023712,
            "question": "In what period did Minimalism emerge as an art style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23661211133003235,
            "question": "How did Minimalism differ from previous art movements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21016377210617065,
            "question": "What are some key characteristics of Minimalism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1639356017112732,
            "question": "What is the impact of Minimalism on contemporary art?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=K. J. Stevens was associated with Minimalism.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7742_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key characteristics of Minimalism?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7742_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Minimalism differ from previous art movements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7742_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what period did Minimalism emerge as an art style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7742_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7742_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7742_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7742_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7742_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7742_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7742_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7742_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7742_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7742_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7742_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while there are documents about Minimalism, and one document mentions an author named K.J. Stevens, it does not mention their association with Minimalism. The information provided only discusses Minimalism as an artistic movement, its characteristics, and the work of artists such as Frank Stella and Donald Judd, but does not provide any connection between K.J. Stevens and this movement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"Stevens\u2019 writing style has been described as minimalist\" and \"K.J.Stevens (born June 4, 1973) is an American novelist and short story writer.\" This information supports the statement that K. J. Stevens was associated with Minimalism."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided to suggest a connection between K.J. Stevens and the Minimalism art movement, whereas the other context information clearly states that Minimalism was an artistic movement associated with artists like Frank Stella and Donald Judd.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}